The video I'm going to explain now is about an
auxiliary registration within the system, a
very important registration for those who use
sales order quotes or need to
do financial planning
in purchase orders and issuing
tax documents, which is the
payment condition. So I can create a
pre-registered payment condition
within the system, and the system will automatically generate it
for you: two installments, three installments,
30, 60, 90, and so on, according to your registration.
So I'm going to show you how to do this
within the system. Here in the
system, you'll go to sales, registrations,
payment conditions (you
can also search here), and in the
payment condition section, how it works:
every time I add a
payment condition, I'll identify the
method. So, for example, I'll
register here 30, 60, and 90. The system
has no idea what 30, 60, and 90 means, so
here I need to identify the number
of installments that correspond to 30, 60, and 90. So,
in this case, there are three installments.
So, there are three schedules that I'll
make. If, for example, it were one more, it would be
30, 60, and 90.  90 is 120, so here are four
installments. I change it to number four.
When I click save, the system
will separate these installments for you, right?
That I need to schedule, but you can't
see that this is 30 and 60.
So I need to identify that
according to the base date I'm
scheduling, for example, today is the 15th, so it
's the 15th plus 30 days, so it will
schedule for the 15th of
next month, so here, 60, here, 90, according to
your payment schedule. And then the
system can make the
due dates correctly. As you
scheduled, click save, it will be
here with the description that I can
change and also with the installments that I have
already scheduled. When I click back
here, it shows me all the installments and
conditions that I have already set up. I
can also link the bank and the type of payment if
I want, or even if it's in the
sales order, I can link it to any
bank and any type of payment. So this is
a feature of the system that
allows you to schedule the
installments and the payment conditions
you work with.